autozmagz.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Auto Repair Manual Free Download and Reviews

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Our advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Google. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about these practices, used by Google, or to opt out of having cookies set on your system, please visit Google’s Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy page.  
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

NOTICE: autozmagz.com is NOT affiliated with all the car manufacturers mentioned throughout the site.  
Car manufacturer names and logos used throughout autozmagz.com belong to the individual companies and are used for identification purposes only

**Related Items:** [ford mondeo mk3 service modul](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/ford+mondeo+mk3+service+modul), [troubleshooting ford ka abs light](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/troubleshooting+ford+ka+abs+light), [DIAGRAM OF FORD KA BRAKE DRUMS](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/DIAGRAM+OF+FORD+KA+BRAKE+DRUMS), [diagramas ecu toyota 3c](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/diagramas+ecu+toyota+3c), [nissan fault code E38](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/nissan+fault+code+E38), [where is the starter one38](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/where+is+the+starter+one38), [2001 lexus es300 manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/2001+lexus+es300+manual), [free downloadauto repair manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/free+downloadauto+repair+manual), [download Free Repair manual 2006 chevy trailblazer](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/download+Free+Repair+manual+2006+chevy+trailblazer), [Chevy Trailblazer Repair Manual free](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Chevy+Trailblazer+Repair+Manual+free), [Free repair Manual for a 1992 Lexus es300](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Free+repair+Manual+for+a+1992+Lexus+es300), [Free Downloadable Auto Repair Manuals](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Free+Downloadable+Auto+Repair+Manuals), [toyota highlander brake diagram](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/toyota+highlander+brake+diagram), [schematic diagram plymouth duster front suspension](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/schematic+diagram+plymouth+duster+front+suspension), [Free Downloadable Auto Repair Manuals porsche](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Free+Downloadable+Auto+Repair+Manuals+porsche), [93 plymouth acclaim timing belt diagram](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/93+plymouth+acclaim+timing+belt+diagram), [free repair manual for a 2006 chevy hhr](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/free+repair+manual+for+a+2006+chevy+hhr), [Free Downloadable Auto Repair Manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Free+Downloadable+Auto+Repair+Manual), [how to download files from autozmagz](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/how+to+download+files+from+autozmagz), [kia magentis repair manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/kia+magentis+repair+manual), [autozmagz](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/autozmagz), [free downloadable truck repair manuals](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/free+downloadable+truck+repair+manuals), [autozmagz com](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/autozmagz+com), [downloadable saturn repair manuel](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/downloadable+saturn+repair+manuel), [Free Downloadable Auto Repair Manuals oldsmobile](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Free+Downloadable+Auto+Repair+Manuals+oldsmobile), [Chevy Hhr Repair Manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Chevy+Hhr+Repair+Manual), [free downloadable auto manuals](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/free+downloadable+auto+manuals), [free downloadable auto repair manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/free+downloadable+auto+repair+manual), [Chevy Trailblazer Repair Manual](http://www.autozmagz.com/search/Chevy+Trailblazer+Repair+Manual)
